## ADETAYO BOLUWATIFE

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

18 Oluwasanmi close
Lagos, Nigeria
+234 8091227084
samuelchristiana38@gmail
.com
github.com/Bhbee
linkedin.com/in/bhbee

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **DIVINE COMPUTER INSTITUTE,** Lagos Nigeria. — IT Instructor

04/2017 - 08/ 2017

I worked with a team of five(5) in this company as an intern.

- Planned 65% of the lessons and activities that facilitate students' acquisition of basic computer skills.
- Also designed and updated all instructional materials for IT programs on a regular basis.
- Gave instructions in a manner that developed the students' confidence in their abilities as computer literate.
- Supervised approximately 50% of the opening and closing of the laboratory, and provide information during a training session in the classroom
- Was also in charge of downloading 2 of 5 important software updates and maintaining hardware.
- Helped ensure that students' systems are in a good state.

#### MALIYO GAME DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP — Cell Lead

08/2021-12/2021

I was assigned to be a cell lead during this five(5) months program

- Organized weekly group meeting to check on the cell members, their achievements so far in the program, challenges faced and receive feedback.
- Was 100% in charge of meeting with the cell mentors that have years of experiences in game development and publishment, fix a convenient time and day for them to have a virtual meeting the cell members

#### **ABOUT ME**

A Computer Scientist and a Software Engineer looking forward to gaining experience in the tech field and developing innovative software. Beyond just writing code, I am knowledgeable in the importance of testing, system analysis and design, and logging. Problem-Solving is one of my major drives to learning.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript | Python |
NodeJS
HTML | CSS | React
Source-Control | Git |
Github

SQL | MySQL | MongoDB

Unity | C#

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Public Speaking
- Technical writing
- Team Leadership

- Made weekly reports on the wellness and challenges faced by the cell members to the organizers.
- Did 80% of the assignment of tasks to cell members during the project phase.
- Was also tasked with helping cell members get solutions to problems encountered during the course of the program.
- Logical thinking
- Excellent Communication

## **EDUCATION**

## **UNIVERSITY OF LAGOS,** — BSc

2018 - 2024

**Computer Science** 

## YABA COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY, Lagos— OND

2016 - 2018

Computer Science, Gradated with Upper Credit.

## ALX\_AFRICA, — DIPLOMA

2022 - 2023

Software Engineering.

#### **PORTFOLIO**

https://react-portfolio-weld-two.vercel.app/

#### **PROJECTS**

- Nine(9) android game prototypes.
- Blog site api
- Project management api
- Portfolio using react
- Meme generator

## LANGUAGE(S)

• English